export const jsQuizz = {
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Select the word with a different pronunciation.",
        choices: [
          "Light",
          "Fight",
          "Might",
          "Sight",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Sight",
      },
      {
        question:
          "________ is the first alphabet in spanish",
          type: "FillB",
          correctAnswer: "a",
      },
      {
        question: "Which word has a distinct pronunciation?",
        choices: ["Chair", "Bear", "Stare", "Share"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Bear",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The English alphabet consists of _____ letters.",
          type: "FillB",
          correctAnswer: "26",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The last letter of the alphabet is _____.",
          type: "FillB",
          correctAnswer: "z",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The letter 'K' comes before the letter 'L' in the alphabet, and it follows the letter _____.",
          type: "FillB",
          correctAnswer: "j",
      },
      {
        question:
          "The vowels in the English alphabet are A, E, I, O, and ____ ",
          type: "FillB",
          correctAnswer: "u",
      },

      {
        question:
          "Which word is pronounced differently ?",
        choices: [
          "Sweet",
          "Seat",
          "Meet",
          "Feet",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Sweet",
      },


      {
        question: "Identify the word with a different pronunciation.",
        choices: [
          "Glass",
          "Brass",
          "Grass",
          "Class",
        ],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Glass",
      },


      {
        question:
          "Choose the word pronounced differently.",
        choices: ["Jump", "Bump", "Lump", "Plump"],
        type: "MCQs",
        correctAnswer: "Plump",
      },
      
    ],
  };